Guide to the Terence Sellers Papers 1967-2000 MSS.167
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series IV: Writing, 154635
  - Subseries C: Artwork for Terence Sellers' books, 154648
    - The Obsession: Carl Apfelschnitt's charcoal drawings published in 1986 edition, [1985]; 154651 (Box 9, Folder 395)
    - The Obsession: etchings by Carl Apfelschnitt, [1985-1986]; 154650 (Box 9, Folder 396)
    - The Obsession: Five duplicate etchings by Carl Apfelschnitt, 1985-1986; 154649 (Box 9, Folder 397)
  - Subseries D: Scrapbooks, 154646
    - Scrapbook compiled by Terence Sellers containing various printed materials relating to her publications., 154647 (Box 10, Folder 398)
  - Subseries E: Publications, 154636
    - Dirty, No.6, January-February 1981; 154645 (Box 15, Folder 402)
    - Dirty, No.8/9, 1983; 154644 (Box 15, Folder 403)
    - Fantacy Register, Issue #2, 1980; 154643 (Box 15, Folder 406)
    - Heavy Metal, 1985; 154641 (Box 15, Folder 408)
    - High Times, No.42, 1979; 154640 (Box 15, Folder 409)
    - Masquerade Magazine, Vol. 7, No.1, 1998; 154639 (Box 15, Folder 411)
    - Skin Two, No.10, undated; 154638 (Box 15, Folder 415)
    - X Magazine, Vol. 1, 1977; 154637 (Box 15, Folder 419)
- Series V: Photographic Materials, 154617
  This series contains photographs, negatives and slides taken of Terence Sellers and Angel Stern. They are arranged alphabetically by photographer.
  - Prints and negatives of photographs taken by Steve Anderson of Terence Sellers., 1973; 154634 (Binder 1, Folder 422)
  - Contact sheets of photographs taken by Amy Arbus of Terence Sellers., 1981; 154633 (Binder 1, Folder 423)
  - Photographic prints, negatives, and contact sheets taken by Christopher Coe., c.1972; 154632 (Binder 1, Folder 424)
  - Prints and negatives from the "Dungeon Photos" series by Jimmy De Sana of Terence Sellers and unknown model. Binder also includes 2 CD's containing digital image files of the full photo series., 1978-1979; 154631 (Binder 1, Folder 425)
  - Prints, negatives, and contact sheets taken by George Du Bose of Terence Sellers, 1982; 154630 (Binder 2, Folder 426)
  - Photographic prints by Doris Kloster of Terence Sellers., undated; 154629 (Binder 2, Folder 427)
  - Photographs by Tony Mendoza of Terence Sellers and Lucian., [1980]; 154628 (Binder 2, Folder 428)
  - Photographic prints, negatives, and contact sheets by Bobby Miller of Terence Sellers and Angel Stern., various; 154627 (Binder 2, Folder 429)
  - Photographic prints by Anya Philips of Terence Sellers., 1970s; 154626 (Binder 2, Folder 430)
  - Contact sheets of "Dr. Stern" taken by Michael Renciwisz, [1990]; 154625 (Binder 3, Folder 431)
  - Negatives of "Mistress Angel" by Chuck Sillery, undated; 154624 (Binder 3, Folder 432)
  - Contact sheets and negatives by Seth Tillet of Terence Sellers., [1980]; 154623 (Binder 3, Folder 433)
  - Contact sheets, negatives and stills from "The Film that was Never Made" by Gordon Stevenson, 1980-1981; 154622 (Binder 3, Folder 434)
  - Still photographs from film by Harold Vogel, 1984-1985; 154621 (Binder 3, Folder 435)
  - Photographic prints of Terence Sellers by Marti Wilkerson, 1997; 154620 (Binder 3, Folder 436)
  - Photographic prints, negatives, and slides of Terence Sellers by unknown photographers, various; 154619 (Binder 3, Folder 437)
  - Slides: Terence Sellers, Green Nude on Beach (photographer unknown), 1975; 157262 (Binder 3, Folder 437 A)
  - Negatives and Photograph: Beach-Grandma, Angel Stern (photographer unknown), 1988; 157263 (Binder 3, Folder 437 B)
  - Slides for Stern Magazine (Germany). Terence Sellers as "whore", Jeffrey Bretschneider as "pimp" (photographer unknown), c.1983; 157264 (Binder 3, Folder 437 C)
  - Negatives: Paris and Venice (photographer unknown), 1974; 157265 (Binder 3, Folder 437 D)
  - Matted 8x10 photograph of Terence Sellers by unknown photographer, undated; 154618 (Box 15, Folder 438)
- Series VI: Business, 154601
  This series contains business related documents and materials related to Seller's career in New York City as Angel Stern.
  - "Book of Beasts", 1989-1991; 154616 (Box 15, Folder 439)
  - Client Cards, 1980s-2000; 154614 (Box 15, Folder 440)
  - Client Cards, continued, 1980s-2000; 154613 (Box 15, Folder 441)
  - Client Cards, continued, 1980s-2000; 154612 (Box 15, Folder 442)
  - Client Cards, continued, 1980s-2000; 154611 (Box 15, Folder 443)
  - Client Cards, continued, 1980s-2000; 154610 (Box 15, Folder 444)
  - Client Cards, continued, 1980s-2000; 154609 (Box 15, Folder 445)
  - Client Cards, continued, 1980s-2000; 154608 (Box 15, Folder 446)
  - Financial Ledger, 1982; 154605 (Box 15, Folder 452)
  - Financial Notes, undated; 154604 (Box 15, Folder 453)
  - Mistress Cards, 1980s-1990s; 154615 (Box 15, Folder 454)
  - "Stan Book", 1992-1993; 154603 (Box 15, Folder 455)
  - Terence Sellers AKA Angel Stern, original envelope with annotations., undated; 154602 (Box 15, Folder 456)
  - Timesheets, 1987; 154607 (Box 15, Folder 457)
  - Timesheets, continued, 1987; 154606 (Box 15, Folder 458)
- Series VII: Academic and Biographical Materials, 154586
  Series includes materials relating to Sellers college studies and personal biographical information.
  - Materials from this folder have been moved to Series I, Folder 127C, 1946; 154600 (Box 11, Folder 459)
  - Author's Resume, 1977-1988; 154599 (Box 11, Folder 460)
  - Categories on Interpretation of Prior Analytics, undated; 154596 (Box 11, Folder 461)
  - Cratylus, St. Augustine, Sophist, undated; 154595 (Box 11, Folder 462)
  - Grec Autres Poesus, undated; 154592 (Box 11, Folder 463)
  - Greek Notebooks, undated; 154594 (Box 11, Folder 464)
  - Greek Notebooks, undated; 154593 (Box 11, Folder 465)
  - Mistress Sterling, The Chameleon, undated; 154591 (Box 11, Folder 466)
  - Nietzche Notes, undated; 154590 (Box 11, Folder 467)
  - Notes from "Rhetoric of Eros: De Sade and Sacher Masoch", undated; 154589 (Box 11, Folder 468)
  - Notes on Dispersement of Manuscripts, 1995-1996; 154597 (Box 9, Folder 469)
  - Resume, 1993-1994; 154598 (Box 9, Folder 470)
  - Sociology Papers, 1983-1984; 154588 (Box 11, Folder 471)
  - "Trix of the Trade" in The Face, 1983; 154587 (Box 11, Folder 472)
- Series VIII: Media, 154579
  This series includes audiocassettes that Sellers recorded in the 1970s. Materials include a recorded interview with Jimmy De Sana for Vacation Magazine in 1981 as well as recordings of Sellers reading her own poems and text from her published writing.
  - Subseries A: Sound recordings, 156676
    Conditions Governing Access
    Access copies for some materials are available by appointment for reading room viewing and listening only. Please contact fales.library@nyu.edu, 212-998-2596.
    - Poem, Radio Music, Disposable Epidermis '73; Susan and Terry Being 'tots' '73, Valium-Cool poem, Gangster of Love, other bad poems, Mark reading poems '74, 1973-1974; ID: 167.0001; 154585 (Box 14, Media ID: 167.0001, Case 167.0001)
      Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements note
      Original format: Audiocassette. Brand Unknown, Tape Capacity Unknown
      Existence and Location of Copies
      CD access copy available.
      Currently available.
    - Neil and Terence Deranged Radio Show, Paranoid Mabel, and Frank as Feces Poet; Obsession reading, 1973;1976; ID: 167.0002; 154584 (Box 14, Cassette 167.0002, E-records fales_mss167, E-records 167.0002)
      Original format; Audiocassette. Hitachi C-120
    - Interview with Jimmy de Sana for VACATION, "Foreigner" dialogue between Eric Mitchell and T.S.; The Cannibal Mouth, 1981; ID: 167.0003; 154583 (Box 14, Media ID: 167.0003, Case 167.0003)
      Original format: Audiocassette, Scotch C-60
    - Impotence Con't; Ennui, Alice Cooper. First Night with Jules, L'Azur par Mallarme, To Libertines, Marquis de Sade, January 6, 1977; 1973; ID: 167.0004; 154582 (Box 14, Media ID: 167.0004, Case 167.0004)
      Original format: Audiocassette, Memorex AD 60
    - Alexander Weinstock Incident, related to Marie Stanley ms; Correct Sadist early text overlaid with poems... Part III, 1974;1978; ID: 167.0005; 154581 (Box 14, Media ID: 167.0005, Case 167.0005)
    - Obscene Phone Calls, Fire Dream (con't), undated; ID: 167.0006; 154580 (Box 14, Media ID: 167.0006, Case 167.0006)
      Original format: Audiocassette, Memorex 60
    - Interview with Jerzy Skolimowski, November 9, 1979; ID: 167.0007; 156673 (Box 14, Media ID: 167.0007, Case 167.0007)
      Original format: Audiocassette, TDK D-C90
    - The Correct Sadist - Excerpts - Reading, May 18, 1980; ID: 167.0008; 156674 (Box 14, Media ID: 167.0008, Case 167.0008)
      Original format: Audiocassette, Data Packaging Dictation D-60
- Series IX: Computer Disks, 160377
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains two disks of photographic material from Terence Sellers' collaboration with Jimmy de Sana on his "Submission" project.
  - Subseries A: Computer Media, 160379
    Born-digital materials have not been preserved and may not be available to researchers.
    - Jimmy de Sana "Submission" Outtakes (Mac version), 1978-9; ID 167.0009; 160375 (Box 14, Media ID 167.0009)
      Format: Data CD
      Currently not available.
    - Jimmy de Sana "Submission" Outtakes (PC version), 1978-9; ID 167.0010; 160376 (Box 14, Media ID 167.0010)
- OVERSIZE Series IV: Writing, 154576
  - Subseries B: Book-length Works, 157259
    - The Correct Sadist: Promotional Materials, unknown; 157266 (Box 12, Folder 246 A)
    - The Correct Sadist: Times Square Show Reading, poster, 1980; 154578 (Box 9, Folder 261 B)
    - The Obsession: Boards, 1985-1986; 154577 (Box 9, Folder 356 B)
  - Subseries E: Publications, 154561
    - BOMB, vol.1, issue 1, 1981; 154575 (Box 12, Folder 399)
    - BOMB, vol.1, issue 2, 1982; 154574 (Box 12, Folder 400)
    - BOMB, no.4, 1982; 154573 (Box 12, Folder 401)
    - East Village Eye Vol.5, No.44, 1984; 154572 (Box 12, Folder 404)
    - FAD, undated; 154571 (Box 12, Folder 405)
    - File Magazine, Vol.3, No.4, 1977; 154642 (Box 15, Folder 407)
    - Impulse, 1983; 154570 (Box 12, Folder 410)
    - Screw, No. 1276, 1993; 154569 (Box 12, Folder 412)
    - Screw, No. 1479, 1997; 154568 (Box 12, Folder 413)
    - Screw, No. 1480, 154567 (Box 12, Folder 414)
    - Article from Soldes de Fin de Series, No. 6, 1979; 154566 (Box 12, Folder 416)
    - Soldes Magazine, 1979-80; 154565 (Box 12, Folder 417)
    - Vacation, No. 4, 1980; 154564 (Box 12, Folder 418)
    - X Magazine, Vol. 2, Issues 2-3, 1978; 154563 (Box 12, Folder 420)
    - X Magazine, Vol.2, issues 4-6, 1978; 154562 (Box 12, Folder 421)
- OVERSIZE Series V: Photographic Materials, 154558
  - Prints, some taken by George Du Bose of Terence Sellers., ca. 1982; 154560 (Box 12, Folder 426 A)
  - BUY Contortions LP, Cover photograph by Anya Philips, 1979; 154559 (Box 12, Folder 430A)
  - Photo-collage of Terence "Suffering From Ennui at the Pink Teacup", ca. 1970s; 273658 (Box 12)
- OVERSIZE Series VI: Business, 154552
  - Desk Calendars, November 1983-August 1984, 1983-1984; 154557 (Box 13, Folder 447)
  - Desk Calendars, February 1985-December 1987, 1985-1987; 154556 (Box 13, Folder 448)
  - Desk Calendars, January-December, 1988; 154555 (Box 13, Folder 449)
  - Desk Calendars, January-October, 1989; 154554 (Box 13, Folder 450)
  - Desk Calendars, January 1990-September 1992, 1990-1992; 154553 (Box 13, Folder 451)
- Unprocessed Materials (Folder oversize folder, Item 2, Folder oversize box folder x)